I want to but I'm a little scared it's just
хочется но немножко боязно просто
interesting It's cool that in your
интересно получается Прикольно вот у вас
Russian Federation a person is not afraid to
в Российской Федерации человек не боится
come to Mexico or Brazil Yes to
приехать в Мексику или в Бразилию Да на
another continent But he is afraid to travel around
другой Континент Но боится поехать по
his own country Yes we've already seen each other a couple of times
своей стране Да виделись уже пару раз
Yes what about the Chechens didn't come
виделись Да что там чеченцы не приехали
For
За
you No I want  And what should I do
тобой Нет я хотите А что надо сделать
to get them to come and show their passport and say,
чтобы приехали паспорт показать сказать
Like, why this?
Типа этот
I never said anything
а зачем Я же никогда не говорил ничего
against them. Well, tell them and they'll come tomorrow. But I
против не Ну скажи и приедут завтра а я
have nothing against them. Why? I don't
же против них ничего не имею Зачем не
even know. Studying the Chechen wars, I
знаю я даже Изучая чеченские войны
came to the conclusion that we are a little ahead of
пришёл к выводу что мы немножко перед
them.  guilty Well, the Russian Federation
ними виноваты Ну Российской Федерации
wow, guilty Well, agree, isn't it
вау ну виноваты Ну согласитесь разве не
so, and how is there peace where?
так а как покоя деже
I mean,
В
they invested a lot of money there,
деньгами очень много денег туда вложили
sweat, money And you recognized the murder,
поте деньгами А вы признали убийство
genocide of peaceful residents of Chechnya Well,
геноцид мирных жителей чеченских Ну
officially Probably not Well, how many
официально Наверное нет Ну вот сколько
thousands, 30,000 children alone
тысяч 30.000 детей только
died Well, the same number as  for six months
погибло Ну столько же сколько за полгода
in Palestine Well, so what No, well, I don't know
в палестине Ну и чего Не ну я не знаю
Palestine is not Palestine Do you specifically
Палестина не Палестина Вы же конкретно
want to apologize to the Chechens for
хотите перед чеченцами извиниться за
these children or not? Personally, I
этих детей или нет лично я
apologize, but I didn't participate in this, I
извиняю но я в этом не участвовал я ещ
was still little, okay, but how are you
маленький был хорошо а как вот вы
specifically ready in front of the Chechen people?
конкретно готовы перед чеченским народом
apologize so everyone has already apologized already
извиниться так всё уже извинились уже де
but I just apologized And that's it yes we
а просто я извинился И всё да мы
have arranged Well the Chechen Republic is very
обустроили Ну чеченскую Республику очень
good a lot of money has been invested there now it's
хорошо много денег вложено сейчас там
beautiful
красота
come and have a look if it's possible
приезжайте посмотрите если есть возможно
Well you won't get out of Ukraine anywhere nano although
Ну вы с Украины никуда нано выйдете хотя
you most likely live somewhere in Poland
вы скорее всего в Поль где-нибудь жите в
Czechoslovakia Czechoslovakia
Чехословакии Чехословакии
I am a citizen of Czechoslovakia I
я ж Я же гражданин Чехословакии Я же вам
told you Well, I can't I don't have
рассказывал Так ну я же не могу у меня
that kind of memory I can't remember thousands of people with
не такая память тысячи человек с
whom I communicate
которыми я общаюсь не могу всех
Czechoslovakia - by the way, there is
запомнить Чехословакия - это кстати
no such country in the Czech Republic anymore yes You
такой страны уже нету в Чехии да Вы
live in
живёте в
Czechoslovakia Well, no  such a country is
Чехословакии Ну нет такой страны есть
the Czech Republic there is Slovakia there is there is
Чехия есть Словакия есть есть есть
Czechoslovakia Czech Republic and Slovakia In
Чехословакия Чехия и Словакия В
ninety-three when
девяносто третьем году когда
Czechoslovakia was divided into the Czech Republic and
Чехословакия разделялась на Чехию и
Slovakia Yes uh they took a transition period of
Словакию Да ээ взяли переходной период
50 years that is there are Czechs
50 лет то есть есть чехи
its organs parliament president there is
её органы парламент президент есть
Slovakia and the organs of Czechoslovakia remained
Словакия и остались органы Чехословакии
because many people They  they do not recognize
потому что многие люди Они не признают
the Czech Republic and Slovakia separately, just like
отдельно Чехию и Словакию так же как у
you have people who are citizens of the USSR who did not
вас есть люди граждане СССР которые не
accept passports at all here No, no, we did
приняли паспорта совсем уже тут Нет нет
not accept passports of the Russian Federation
не приняли паспорта Российской Федерации
or Ukraine, yes, because I
или Украины у нас да потому что они
think they were born in the USSR and according to
считаю Они рождены в СССР и По
international law, while it
международному законодательству пока ээ
still lives  uh at least one person who
живёт ещё ээ хоть один человек который
is the holder of a passport born in
есть обладателем паспорта рождённого в
this country must serve that is, there
этой стране долж обслуживать то есть
is, as it were, such an army does not exist in
есть как бы таких армии нету
Czechoslovakia Yes, but the bodies that
Чехословакии Да но органы которые
serve there pay pensions
обслуживают там пенсии выплачивают
Czechoslovakian, as it were, how is
чехословацкий
it with you, the Civil Code, how is it in
ещё как бы как это у вас закс как это
your opinion, the Civil Code, it seems Well, yes there  where do
по-вашему закс вроде Ну да там где
they register
регистрируют
death and birth yet If
вот смерть рождение ещё Если
Czechoslovaks yes there is such an interesting well
чехословаков да есть такое интересно ну
when I was in the Czech Republic in Prague there
когда я был в Чехии в Праге там столи
was the capital of the
была
Slovaks the capital Prague and Bratislava
пра словаки столица Прага а Братислава
not Well look come on look when
не Ну смотри давай так вот смотри когда
was the Soviet Union the capital of the Soviet
был Советский Союз столица Советского
Union what
Союза какая
was Moscow and the capital of the Russian
была Москва а столица российской
Soviet  Federal Socialist
Советской Федеративной Социалистической
Republic what was also Moscow that's
Республики какая была тоже Москва вот
all the same and with the Czech Republic with Czechoslovakia
всё также и с Чехии с Чехословакии
Bratislava what is considered in the Czech Republic how does it
Братислава чем считается в Чехии как
relate Well in my opinion yes bratis
относится Ну по-моему да братис
Bratislava is in
Братислава это в
Slovakia well it is considered some kind of
Словакии хорошо она считается какойто
Bratislava Bratislava is the capital of Slovakia
Братислава Братислава столица Словакии
Prague is the capital of the Czech Republic and Prague is the capital of
Прага столица Чехии и Прага столица
Czechoslovakia as well as  look Kiev was the
Чехословакии так же как смотри Киев был
capital of the Ukrainian Soviet
столицей украинской Советской
Socialist Republic Moscow is
Социалистической Республики Москва
the capital of the Russian Soviet
столица российско Советской
Federative Russian Soviet
Федеративной российской Советской
Federative Socialist Republic
Федеративной Социалистической Республики
and Moscow is simultaneously the capital of the USSR it
и Москва одновременно столицей СССР
would be
бы
good with such
хорошо с такой
a legend Ask the local
леген Тесь поспрашивайте местное
population they think that they live in
население они считают что они живут в
Czechoslovakia Yes look uh
Чехословакии Да смотри ээ гражданами
4% consider themselves citizens of Czechoslovakia
Чехословакии себя себя считают ээ 4%
population of the Czech Republic and 35% of the population of Slovakia
населения Чехии и 35% населения Словакии
most people most people yes
большинство людей большинство людей да
They changed their passports to Czech passports
Они поменяли паспорта на паспорта Чехии
Slovak passports But I'm telling you We have
паспорта Словакии Но я же говорю У нас у
an association yes Here's such a 4% of
нас ассоциация есть да Вот такая 4% у
our population in the Czech Republic and 3 with or there
нас в Чехии население и 3 с по или там
3.7 with  - I think they had it in Slovakia they did
3,7 по-моему у них было в Словакии они
n't change the passports either I didn't change the
не поменяли паспорта тоже я не поменял
passports Well, as a passport I already receive de
паспорта Ну как паспорт Я уже получаю де
in that my birth certificate
в том что у меня свидетельство о
was
рождении было
Czechoslovakian Czechoslovakian passport I
чехословацкое чехословацкое паспорт Я
already received after ninety-third
уже получал после девяносто третьего
year So I could also receive as a
года Вот и я мог получить как паспорт
Czech passport  if I want to become a citizen of the
Чехии если я захочу стать гражданином
Czech Republic so And with a passport, a passport of
Чехии так И паспортом паспорт
Czechoslovakia because I was born in
Чехословакии потому что я рождён в
Czechoslovakia That is, look, on the
Чехословакии То есть у нас смотри на
territory of the Czech Republic there are two
территории Чехии существует два
state entities, the new Czech Republic
государственных образования новое Чехия
and the transitional Czechoslovakia, that is, it is
и переходное Чехословакия то есть оно
already supported by 4% yes, yes, it is,
уже которы 4% поддерживает да да оно
look, it is not like  does not conclude new
смотри оно не как бы не заключает новые
international agreements, for example, from the Czech Republic, Slovakia, and the
международные договора так например от
Czech Republic, separately, conclude new agreements separately. Yes, but
отдельно Чехия отдельно Словакия Да но
there are international agreements that
есть международные договора которые ещё
Czechoslovakia also serves, that is,
обслуживают Чехословакия то есть есть у
we have certain bodies. Well, how are these not
нас определённые органы Ну как это не
authorities? You can say that these are quasi-
органы власти можно сказать это квази
organs, so they exist for
органы такие так они существуют для
administration.  these
администрирования вот этих
uh that were there before there are contracts
ээ которые были раньше там договора
administration of pensions
администрирование пенсии
administration of various social
администрирование разных там социальных
payments And so on and so
выплат И так
forth is good Listen I won't argue but
дальше хорошо Слушай не буду спорить а
just with you Look with you with you uh on the
просто у вас Смотри у вас у вас ээ на
territory of the former Soviet Union there is
территории бывшего Советского Союза там
a little bit different the collapse of the Soviet
немножко по-другому распад Советского
Union happened in Czechoslovakia  we
Союза прошёл в Чехословакии у нас это
had it by mutual agreement of the Czech Republic and
было по обоюдному договору Чехии и
Slovakia And you all just
Словакии А у вас всё просто там
flew apart there and therefore did not have time to make
разлетелось и поэтому не успели сделать
this transition but it was there was even When
этот переходной но было было даже Когда
Yeltsin already signed the agreements in these Belovezhskaya
Ельцин подписывал уже в этих беловежских
Pushcha
пуще
and already as if it were not the USSR
соглашения и уже как бы было ни сссра
as if it were already He put a signature that  no
как бы уже Он поставил подпись что нет
but Gorbachev was still Gorbachev was still
но Горбачёв ещё был Горбачёв ещё
functioning that's when on what day
функционировал вот когда в какой день
the USSR ended what do you
закончился СССР Как ты
think I don't remember the month day like the
думаешь я месяц день не помню типа
Belovezhskaya agreements they In ninety-
беловежские соглашения они В девяносто
one In ninety-one Yes at the
первом году В девяносто первом Да в
end of ninety-one December Yes yes
конце девяносто первого декабрь Да да
yes Then I well not really You see  Yes, and
да Дальше я ну не очень Вот видишь Да а
the bodies are the Constitutional Court of
органы это конституционный суд
the Soviet Union, the Supreme Council
Советского Союза Верховный Совет
continued to function, that is, at the
продолжал функционировать то есть
same time, you just didnt have this process
одновременно у у вас просто этот процесс
dragged on, we made a transition
не затянулся у нас сделали переходной
period so that there would be no conflicts,
период для того чтобы не было конфликтов
so we made a transition period of 50 years, and
вот сделали переходной период 50 лет а у
you because you didnt do it
вас из-за того что не сделали переходной
you had this transitional period, this
период у вас был вот этот
constitutional crisis of
конституционный кризис де
the year because the Constitution was still
года потому что Конституция ещё была
Soviet and
Советская а
Yeltsin, according to the Soviet Constitution, did not have
Ельцин по Советской Конституции не имел
the authority to dissolve parliament
полномочий распускать парламент потому
because in the Soviet Union the Supreme Council
что в Советском Союзе Верховный Совет он
was higher than the General Secretary so there was no president
был выше генсека так не было президента
and Yeltsin then shot the parliament
да Ельцин тогда расстрелял парламент
when it was like that  do you remember this in
Когда было так вы помните это В
ninety-three you know this is
девяносто третьем году знаете Это
the shooting of parliament not the state emergency committee this is de per
расстрел парламент не гкчп это де пер
year the state emergency committee this is the collapse of August August
год гкчп это развал август август
per and the collapse of the USSR yes and this is the October
пер и развал ССР да а это Октябрьский
this Yeltsin coup shooting of
этот ельцинский переворот расстрел
parliament shooting of the White House I
парламента расстрел Белого Дома я всё
want to ask you all the time I'm trying to find
хочу вас спросить Я пытаюсь найти
a second in the Czech Republic before  still crowns
секундочку в Чехии до сих пор кроны
now both crowns and euros are in circulation
сейчас и кроны и евро параллельно ходят
And when I was there there were only crowns the rate
А я когда был Там только кроны были курс
was 2 from the pono to the ruble now how has it
был 2 с поно к рублю сейчас как
changed Wait are you Czech or
поменялось Подождите вы чешские или
Czechoslovak
чехословацкие
crowns well
кроны ну
not we have three currencies So
не у нас ходит три валюты Так ну
officially every store must
официально каждый магазин должен
accept the first euro  since we are in
принимать первое евро поскольку мы в
the European Union, the Czech crowns that were issued
Евросоюзе кроны чешские которые выпущены
in denominations after the third year and the
номиналом после дено третьего года и
Czechoslovak crowns, there are few of them, we are even
чехословацкие кроны их мало вот мы даже
citizens of Czechoslovakia, we are all ready, let's
граждане Чехословакии мы всё уже давайте
forget about the
Забудем про
Czechoslovaks, I explain, I can even
чехословаки я объясняю я вот даже в
calculate in the store with Czech crowns,
магазине рассчитаю с чешскими кронами
yes, a simple answer, you need to answer for a second
уже да простой ответ на секунду вам надо
I say what 2 s on the
ответить Я говорю какой 2 с по кроне
Czech crown or or it increased I don't know
чешской или или он увеличился Я не знаю
what the rate is I will pay in crowns I don't
какой курс Я в кронах рассчитаюсь я не
change the rate of the crown to the dollar I
меняю курс кроны к доллару я я сам
will calculate myself I don't need dollars I don't
посчитаю я я не мне зачем мне доллары Я
know the
не знаю курс
dollar rate I don't buy anything for dollars  I
доллара я не покупаю ничего за доллары Я
buy for crowns I came to the store and
покупаю за кроны Я пришёл в магазине и
buy for crowns Okay, how many crowns
покупаю за кроны Ладно сколько крон
does a bottle of beer cost in the store I dont understand
стоит бутылка пива в магазине не понимаю
again you start saying something like dollars
ещё раз ты начинаешь что-то там доллары
Not dollars, you start
Не доллары какую-то типа начинаешь
saying something like that Yes, Im just curious about me Youre
говорить Да мне просто интересно я Ты
just some kind of damn  you you re Well it
просто какой-то блин ты ты ре Ну ты мне
seems to me that you are some kind of a bore
кажется что ты вот какой-то занудство
eating some kind of dollar exchange rate you you know in your
ешь какой-то курс доллара ты ты в своей
country what the dollar exchange rate is in your country
стране знаешь какой курс доллара у вас
Yes I know why you need to know the dollar exchange rate Well
Да знаю зачем тебе знать курс доллара Ну
because I often travel abroad
потому что я часто езжу за границу мне
it is important to me for  what border do you travel to,
это важно за какую границу ты ездишь
I mean list it or something Yeah, I don't
в смысле перечислить что ли Да ну не
know, last year I was in India, Mexico and
знаю в том году был в Индии в Мексике и
Brazil,
в Бразилии
what got you so far away, yeah, I like to
что тебя так помотала да люблю
travel Cool Where are you from? Near
путешествовать Прикольно А сам откуда ты
Moscow Wait And you've
С под Москвой Подожди А в Чечне ты так и
never been to Chechnya No and  I don't really want to So stop stop
не был Нет и не хочу особо Так стоп стоп
you told me how beautiful it is there
ты мне рассказывал как там красиво
come That is you all when will I
приезжайте То есть ты всю когда я буду
feel safe there now
чувствовать себя там безопасно сейчас
I don't think I will feel
мне не кажется что я там буду себя
comfortable there
комфортно
What is
чувст Что
it damn if only there you know how in
такое блин раз бы там знаете как в
Brazil I didn't really like it either
Бразилии тоже мне не очень понравилось
that is, you are a citizen of the Russian
то есть ты гражданин Российской
Federation and you are in Mexico Where
Федерации и тебе в Мексике Где
drugs in Brazil were more comfortable than in
наркоте в Бразилии было комфортнее чем в
Chechnya depending on where you go in Mexico in
Чечне смотря куда вы поедете в Мексике в
Cancun it was very calm there in
Канкуне был там очень спокойно в
Brazil in ri Zhenya yes there in the evening it is better
Бразилии в ри Женей да там вечером лучше
not to go out on the
не выходить на
street if someone even calls  close
улицу если кто-то даже поз близ
in principle if you do
в принципе если ты там неадекватно себя
n't behave inappropriately there probably nothing
не ведёшь наверное с тобой ничего не
will happen to you Well, anyway it's scary to go there
будет Ну ну всё равно страшно ехать туда
True Well it's somehow already implanted in my brain
Правда Ну это как-то уже в мозгу вложило
yes
да
like I want to but it's a little scary it's just
типа хочется но немножко боязно просто
interesting it turns out It's cool you have a
интересно получается Прикольно вот у вас
person in the Russian Federation  not afraid
в Российской Федерации человек не боится
to go to Mexico or Brazil Yes to
поехать в Мексику или в Бразилию Да на
another Continent But afraid to travel around
другой Континент Но боится ехать по
his own
своей
country Not that I'm afraid I don't
стране Да не то чтобы боюсь я не хочу
really want to Damn you understand what I saw
особо блин понимаете то что я посмотрел
in Mexico and Brazil is hardly more beautiful in Chechnya
в Мексике и Бразилии вряд ли в Чечне
stop stop stop stop you're offending
красивее стоп стоп стоп стоп ты обижаешь
Ramzan now
сейчас Рамзана
Akhmatovich No, there is a different climate there,
ахматовича Нет там другой климат там
you understand, there are no such
понимаете там нет таких Чечне
views in Chechnya when you stand and look
видов когда ты стоишь смотришь
at the sea and at the same time Well, from above Yes,
одновременно на море и на Ну свысока Да
from the shore, damn, this is not in Chechnya, there is no such thing there, there
с берега блин это не в Чечне нету такого
is no ocean, so to speak I like to
там там нету океана так скажем Я люблю
just look at beautiful
просто посмотреть на красивые
places I look at that  You
места я так смотрю что Вы очень хорошо
made peace with the Chechens very well after this
помирились с чеченцами после этой
war, that you have measured it so much that you are
войны что настолько померили что вы
afraid to come to Chechnya.
боитесь в Чечню
Well, I am not saying that I am afraid, I feel
приехать Да я же не говорю что я боюсь
kind of uneasy, so to speak, yes, yes,
мне как бы неспокойно так скажем да да
anxious, anal blow. Well, a little bit. And
тревожно [__] дут Да ну немножко А
you yourself would come
вы сами бы приехали
to me to go there. I understand.  And to Donbass
на мне туда ехать Понятно А на Донбасс
No, well, look Why the hell should I go there,
Не ну там смотри Нахрена мне ехать туда
like in Donbass, Donbass is now
типа на Донбассе на Донбассе сейчас
occupied by Russian troops
оккупированы российскими войсками
Of course I wont go there But Chechnya
Конечно я не приеду туда Так а Чечня
Chechnya is not occupied, its the territory of the
Чечня же не оккупированы это территории
Russian Federation, the laws of the Russian Federation are in effect there,
Российской Федерации там действуют
in
законы Российской Федерации в
order, not only the laws of the Russian
порядке там не только законы Российская
Federation are in force  there are also traditions there,
Федерация дест там свои традиции тоже
like in Tatarstan and in the tower, and so it is
есть как и в Татарстане и в башне и так
necessary to respect, that's why we are
надо уважать просто поэтому мы
multinational, yes, yes, Well, you are
многонационально да да Ну вот вы
respectful. I cannot understand what
уважающий Я не могу понять что с вами
could happen to you. You just came to
может случиться вы просто приехали в
Grozny, went to the station, walked around,
Грозный вышли на вокзал да прошлись
looked at the sights, most
посмотрели достопримечательно скорее
likely nothing.  it won't happen I just do
всего ничего не случится мне просто ну
n't want to yet that's why Yes I
не хочется пока вот почему Да вот я не
can't understand let me as a psychologist
могу понять давайте я как вот психолог
try to understand this deep
попробую понять вот эту вашу глубинную
pain of yours that
боль что вас
scares you doesn't
пугает не
scare you at all Chen they say that adopted
пугает вообще Чен говорят что приемный
people Many people told me this I believe in it
народ Мне многие это говорили я в это
and most likely  if I come there and do
верю и скорее всего если я приеду и буду
n't walk around there I don't know in my underwear on the
там не ходить там не знаю в трусах по
street then everything will be fine if I don't
улице то всё будет нормально если я не
get drunk and make a fuss there no one
буду бухой там бурого буянить никто мне
will say anything bad to me most
там ничего плохого не скажет скорее
likely if I go up to the local youth to
всего если я подойду к местной молодёжи
ask something where I can eat something
что-то спросить где можно покушать
tasty  where can I What to see I will be happy
вкусно где можно Что посмотреть мне с
to tell you everything most likely it
удовольствием всё расскажет скорее всего
will be like that well I just do
так и будет ну просто желания особого
n't have much desire for it yet in Chech Well why
Пока что нету в чеч Ну зачем
I like to see other continents I have
Я люблю другие континенты посмотреть
n't been to Antarctica yet it's
пока не был только в Антарктиде е
just cool it turns out Well like VSS
прикольно просто получается Ну как ВСС
but damn I won't set foot in it  to Chechnya Yes, we
но блин я в это не ногой в Чечню Да мы
made peace I'm not saying that I won't
помирились не говорю что не ногой со
go there in time I'll probably well
временем съезжу наверно ну меня должен
some acquaintance of mine probably from
появиться какой-то знакомый наверно из
Chechnya should appear so that he would receive me as a guest so
Чечни чтобы он меня в гости приня чтобы
that he would guarantee your safety
чтобы он гарантировал вашу безопасность
Yes, not just knowing someone local he will
Да не просто зная кого-то местного он
show you and tell you about everything
тебе ВС покажет расскажет
Well, I don't really want to. Well, look, for
Ну не очень хочется Ну смотри вот
example, people come to a
например люди же приезжают вот в
Muslim country in Turkey, a
мусульманскую страну в Турцию
Muslim country in Egypt, they come as
мусульманскую страну в Египет приезжают
tourists and so on. But they can't go to Chechnya. By the way, have
туристами и и что А в Чечню не
you been to Turkey,
могут Кстати вы были в Турции в Египте
have you been to Egypt and so on. And where did you like it more, both
был и что А где вам больше понравилось
there and there?  there are some peculiarities different
и там и там есть свои особенности разный
climate different level of service Well I
климат разный уровень сервиса Ну мне в
like Turkey better I'll explain why
Турции больше понравится Почему объясню
because when you walk down the
потому что они вот когда ты идёшь по
street past Turkish traders Yes they
улице мимо торговцев турецких Да они
call you but not as actively as in
тебя зазывает но не так активно как в
Egypt in Egypt it's simply unbearable to walk
Египте в Египте просто невыносимо ходить
down the
по
street
улице
Well
Ну
bro And how  you think If you were walking
братан А как вы думаете Если бы вы шли
through Chechnya as
по Чечне как
if I think
бы я думаю
no There is
нет Есть
confidence Yes hardly Well do
уверенность Да вряд ли Ну это по рынку
you mean on the market or just on
вы имеете в виду или просто по
Yes no no one would not bother Hey bro why did
Да не никто бы не не заёб Эй братан что
you come here why did you come sure
ты сюда приехал зачем ты приехал уверен
that no and would  your own people didn't get
что нет и бы свои же не поняли
it You're cool By the way, I forgot We've been with
прикольно вы Кстати я забыл Мы давно с
you for a long time You're a Streamer Yes, I just go there and
Вами вы Стример же Да просто там захожу
let's go No, well, post
так себе погнали Не ну выкладывайте
something on YouTube, you can see that I'm
что-то на YouTube можно посмотреть что
not just fooling around I'm having fun
не просто себе так балуюсь Я развлекаюсь
after
после
work I get it, well, it's provocative there, fla T
работы я понял ну провокационно там фла
-shirts  yes yes I love I have a job I'm
футболочки да да люблю У меня работа я
just a programmer you know you sit all
просто программист знаете сидишь целый
day long in short you crumple like there fingers And here
день короче мнёшь типа там пальцы А тут
you can who are you sitting at the computer You are
можешь ты кто ты сидишь за компом Ты
nobody you are In short a dude an appendage to the computer And
никто ты Короче чувак придаток компу А
here you go out and you are the king You can send
тут выходишь и ты король Можешь послать
someone you can there like a bottle  everything And
кого-то можешь там типа а бутылка всё И
you feel cool and assert yourself
ты себя чувствуешь крутым и само
and I never switch to insults and
и я никогда не перехожу на оскорбление и
swearing And I switch very cool As
маты А я перехожу очень прикольно Как
soon as I hear this I press Dal and
только я это слышу я Дале нажимаю и
do not feel anything at all Well, I am not
вообще никаких не испытываю Ну я не я с
you and I, you see, we had a normal, logical
вами видите мы с вами нормально логично
conversation A  so I can send
поговорили А так я могу и послать
someone like that And why I don't know
кого-то вообще так А зачем я не знаю
like in person one thing then you will be
типа в лицо одно дело тогда ты будешь
considered for yourself Even if you can go up
считаться для себя Даже если ты можешь
to someone on the street who you don't
на улице подойти к тому кто тебе не
like to say in person that you then you
нравится сказать в лицо что ты тогда ты
can feel there No  well wait
можешь там чувствовать Не ну подожди
wait p Look you now damrava
подожди п Смотри ты сечас дамрава
about Chechnya I don't think that you would have told so frankly in the
про Чечню Я не думаю что ты бы в
presence of Akhmat Kadyrov oh Ramzan Kadyrov
присутствии Ахмата Кадырова ой Рамзана
that it is somehow dangerous to walk in Chechnya
откровенно что как-то опасно в Чечне
Yes so well post this video
ходить Да так хорошо выложите это видео
I'm not I'm just saying Well and of course  you would sit like that
я не я просто говорю Ну и конечно ты бы
in front of him, [ __ ],
вживую при нём вообще так сидел такой
really, it depends on where we are.
бля правда смотря где бы мы находились
Listen, I consider him the same person
Слушайте я его считаю таким же человеком
as me, he is in no way superior to me.
как и я ни в коем образе не выше меня он
Maybe I consider him worse than. Well,
Может быть я его хуже считаю чем Ну
look, imagine that you are coming.  in
смотри хорошо представь ты приезжаешь в
Mexico you go on an
Мексику так идёшь на
excursion you go you go you go somewhere
экскурсию идёшь идёшь заходишь где-то
into a gateway and
там в подворот а там заходит тоже
Kadyrov also comes in by chance and he says
Кадыров случайно и он говорит
Oh you told him about Chechnya And what have I
О ты ему сказал про Чечню А что я ничего
not said anything bad about Chechnya No well
плохого не говорил уже про Чечню Не ну
what is there like he is like And you you
что там типа он такой А ты ты в Мексику
I came to Mexico but I didn't come to Chechnya so that you would
приехал а в Чечню не приезжал что бы ты
answer him
ему ответил
temptation like that No well build the same
завлечение так Нет ну постройте такие же
hotels as in Mexico make the same
отели как в Мексике сделайте такие же
resorts I will come That is you want you
курорты я приеду То есть ты хочешь ты
want to offend Kadyrov by saying that
хочешь обидеть Кадырова сказав что у
his hotels are crap in comparison with Mexico
него отстой отели в сравнении с мексикой
not only  he has crap hotels in all of
не только у него отстой оте во всей
Russia, in all of
России во всей
Ukraine and in all of Eastern Europe,
Украине и во всяких восточноевропейских
it's strange when you come to the
странно когда ты приезжаешь на
Mediterranean or somewhere further away,
Средиземное море или куда подальше там
everything is on a different level there, it seems to me that you are
всё на другом уровне Мне кажется ты
walking on a knife edge, you can't tell Kadyrov
ходишь по лезви ножа сказать Кадырову
that his
что у него отстой
hotels are crap, you wouldn't have said it, would you?
отели нельзя так ты бы не сказал ты
often you didn't tell him to his face I wo
часто в лицо ты ему не сказал я сегодня
n't sleep today Why can't I tell Kadyrov to his face
не усну Почему я не могу сказать в лицо
if he asks me What What
Кадырову если он меня спросит Какое Что
would I like to see in Chechnya what would I
бы мне хотелось видеть в Чечне что бы я
like to improve I would tell him what I
хотел улучшить Я бы ему сказал что я
wanted to improve Why not I should Oh what
хотел улучшить Почему нет я должен О что
li when you see Kadyrov wait again do
ли при виде Кадырова подожди ты ещё раз
you imagine that Kadyrov
ты представляешь что Кадыров у тебя
will ask you what to improve in Chechnya it is you
спросит что улучшить в Чечне это ты
such a
такую
situation No no I'm not like that
ситуацию Нет нет я не так
smog he will say something like you didn't go to Chechnya
смоли он скажет типа что ты в Чечню не
but went to Mexico to rest you are not
поехал а поехал в Мексику отдыхать не
patriotic if he does that to me  will
патриотични если он так со мной будет
talk Just if I greet him politely
говорить Просто если я с ним вежливо
Yes I will send him if he
поздороваюсь Да я е пошлю если он мне
tells me What are you doing if we are in
скажет Ты что так если мы будем в
Mexico
Мексике
That is, you will send Kadyrov
находиться То есть ты пошлёшь Кадырова
if he tells you something so he
если он тебе что-то скажет так он не
will not talk to me like that He does
станет со мной так разговаривать У него
not have a  if he says there I will
нет с ес если он там скажет я
him sa When they start talking to me ill-mannered
его са Когда со мной невоспитанной
I can send
начинают разговаривать Я могу послать
anyone I don't care
любого Мне неважно
not You are brave of course really brave But
не Ты смелый конечно реально смелый Но
damn But this joke in short made my
блин Но это шутка короче сделала мой
evening Okay I Okay Okay let's
вечер Хорошо я Ладно Хорошо давай
beat him I
побе я его
sent him I came together
послал Я приехал вме
samra
самра
shoved a letter  on y Telegram right now
засунули пись на й Telegram прямо зараз
axis VN
ось ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube is busy with
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through srg or in your ban and very
нас через срг ор в твый бан и дуже
many videos are not shown to people at times do not
багато видео не показуе людям вчасно не
show information about streams so
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that we Mali operational links are
того щоб мы Мали оперативный звязок
written right now and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegra okrim video tezh tsikava and
телегра окрим видео ще теж цикава и
useful information and we are obliged to you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
trimati constant operational links
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that che will show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukraini letter
YouTube Слава украини пись